Andrew Estefan Venson IV

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-venson-iv-b6935a118/ Portfolio: https://andrewvenson.herokuapp.com

> Github: https://github.com/andrewvenson Email: vensoneandrew@gmail.com Phone: 512-450-4101

Summary

Experienced in writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices. Highly skilled in building secure API integrations and automations. Skilled and knowledgeable in building full stack client side and server side architectured applications. Highly competent in integrating data from various back-end services and databases.

Experience

Lead Applications Developer

Integral Care - Austin, Texas 07/2020 - Present

Full Time: Responsible for developing, testing and maintaining secure web applications, scripts, and automations that integrate with organization's electronic healthcare record amongst a plethora of other APIs. Responsible for migrating core Integral Care services to the cloud.

Languages & Frameworks used: Javascript, Python, C#, TSQL, Cache SQL, Postgres, React, .NET

Software Tester

Smartwebs - Austin, Texas 10/2019 - 12/2019

Full Time: Built automated test framework with JavaScript and Sahi automation tools. Tested mobile applications across Android platforms using Android Studios.

Languages & Frameworks used: Javascript, Sahi

Computer/Software Technician

Austin POS/CRS Solutions - Austin, Texas

10/2016 - 09/2019

Full Time: Installed, configured and programmed innovative Point of Sale menus. Developed internal scripts.

Trained staff, and provided remote support. Lead all Focus Point of Sale projects.

Languages used: Python

Languages / Frameworks / Libraries

Python ● Javascript ● C# ● T-SQL ● MySQL ● PostgreSQL ● Cache SQL ● CSS ● HTML5

Flask ● Express ● .NET ● React Native

React.js ● Jquery

Tools / Skills / OS / API's

Azure ■ AWS ■ Heroku ■ Vercel
Github ■ Git ■ Vim ■ Node.js
Linux ■ Unix ■ Windows
REST ■ SOAP

Education

Full Stack Web Development

Computer Programming

Austin Community College

32 credits